{
    "subject": "resource/Conjure_One_(album)",
    "predicate": "ontology/recordLabel",
    "object": "resource/Nettwerk",
    "human_readable": "The album 'Conjure One' was released by Nettwerk.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8992359638214111,
            "question": "Name an album released by Nettwerk."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8990469574928284,
            "question": "Who released the album 'Conjure One'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8831974864006042,
            "question": "What is the name of the album released by Nettwerk?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8434582948684692,
            "question": "When was the album 'Conjure One' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8039930462837219,
            "question": "What record label released the album 'Conjure One'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7702962756156921,
            "question": "Is 'Conjure One' a studio album?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.706794023513794,
            "question": "What is Nettwerk known for releasing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6939694881439209,
            "question": "Has Nettwerk released other popular albums?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5639593601226807,
            "question": "Are there any famous songs on the album 'Conjure One'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5097264647483826,
            "question": "What genre is the album 'Conjure One' likely to be?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The album 'Conjure One' was released by Nettwerk.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4197_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any famous songs on the album 'Conjure One'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4197_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Nettwerk released other popular albums?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4197_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Nettwerk known for releasing?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4197_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4197_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4197_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4197_113.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4197_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4197_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4197_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4197_84.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4197_91.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4197_98.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4197_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON answer:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that the documents mention the following information related to the triple:\n\n* The album \"Conjure One\" is mentioned as being released on CD in 2002.\n* It is also mentioned that the self-titled debut CD of Conjure One, featuring guest vocalists such as Marie Claire D'Ubaldo, Sinead O'Connor, Chemda, and Poe, is being released by Nettwerk on September 17, 2002."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that the album \"Conjure One\" was released on the Nettwerk label, which supports the given triple."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}